We are zebras, zebras, senkaboko zebras!
So, where are we?
We are in Sendai!
Where is Sendai?
Sendai is Tohoku? Where in Tohoku?
Miyagi!
Miyagi? Where is Miyagi?
Tohoku?
I see.
So, I came to Sendai Station in Miyagi Prefecture for the first time today.
Welcome home!
Sparkling!
More than I expected.
Welcome back!
Since it's your first time in Sendai, you must want to enjoy the city, right?
Yes, that's right.
But it's your first time, so you don't know what to expect.
If you ask around, you'll get to know the best parts of Sendai.
Helping each other?
Yes.
What kind of help?
Japanese friends.
So, let me ask you something.
I'm just wondering if anyone is passing through here, people.
First of all, is it okay if I film on YouTube?
Yes, it's totally fine.
Okay, I understand.
We're called "kaboko" in shimabama.
Yes, I know.
You know? Really?
Will you subscribe to our channel?
Sure.Of course.
Eh, I'm glad.
This happens. It's a totally nice city.
We went to Sendai for the first time.
It's our first time in Sendai, so we don't know anything about it.
I'm wondering if you have any recommendations.
Recommendations?
There's a building called D-Beans.
There are a lot of stores there, and I highly recommend it.
D-BEANS?
D-BEANS.
What a strange name!
Like beans.
And there's something on the first floor.
I recently heard that there are a lot of vending machines at the entrance of the first floor.
You should definitely go there.
Great. Speaking of vending machines, you're a YouTuber.
I'll be there.
Since we're here.
What?
If you can make it, you can play with this.
May I?
Sendai's a nice town.
Have fun.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
I'd like to go again.
I would like to go there.
Pakarappakarappakarappakarappakarappakarappakarappakarappakarappakarappakarappak.
I have just arrived at the vending machine of E-Rings, which was told to me by a businessman in Sendai.
I've just arrived at the place where E-Rings' vending machine is located.We have arrived at the location where E-Rings' vending machine is located.
I would like to introduce them to you.
Wow, there are a lot of them!
Have you ever seen a vending machine for dumpling gel?
I don't think so, have you?
They're a horse's favorite.
Stripes like them, too.
Stripes do.
Yes, sir.
So, I'm looking at gyoza now.
There's one from Mitsuishi, one from Tokyo, and one from Kumamoto.
I'm a little surprised.
The birthplace of yaki-gyoza in Japan
You can eat them from a vending machine!
And it's on the train line!
So, according to the rumor, the businessman who just told me
I told him I'd recommend the gyoza.
He said they sell gyoza from Tokyo and Kumamoto
Gyoza from Tokyo and Kumamoto are sold in the vending machine.
But sometimes they are from different stores.
I'll check back periodically.
Seriously?
Just pop your foot in!
I think you'll enjoy all kinds of dumplings from the vending machine.
Okay, so you want to buy some?
If you're going to go to all this trouble, I'd like to buy some.
Which one do you want?
Which one do I want?
Oh, wow!
There it is!
I forgot.
The usual.
We have to complete the mission.We need to succeed in our mission.
We have to succeed in our mission, right?
What? Today.
What?
Four dice on one at the same time.
I can't!
I can't.
I can't do it.
I did it.
Riki.
You did it.
You can't do it, can you?
I'll edit it. I'll come back later.
I'll get it to you.
I'm not buying it, it's not funny.
It's like a miracle happened.
Then we'll do it again.
Take another one.
And then...
I'd like to shake the roll.
One is zero.
Let's go!
Gyoza!
I'm asleep!
Wait a minute.
You're so lucky.
Sendai's a nice town.
Have you ever seen anything like this?
It happened to me.
We made it!
I'll buy gyoza!I'm buying dumplings!
I'm pushing!
Here it comes!
So this is how it's done.
I bought the legendary salt dumplings.
Salted gyoza.
They have hot pots and stuff.
Oysters!
Amazing.
Tsawaii crab. Oyster nabe.
Mmm...
Just by being in Sendai.
You can enjoy food from all over Japan.
Wow, indeed!
Is this served in a pot, too?
This is just what you see here.
It's also frozen.
It's got all the ingredients.
It looks like the kind you can eat at home.
Wow, that's convenient.
That's nice.
It's a vending machine for takoyaki sweets.
It's a macaron vending machine.
They're animal macarons.
First place in the macaroon category?
That's amazing!
They're absolutely delicious!
Look, look, look.
They're the size of a woman's palm.
Let's get some.
There it is!
And the usual...And again... The usual.
Here we go. I know, I know.
Okay, here we go.
Let's go!
30-digit practice rate.
I'll go.
I'm going.
Are you sure you're going?
Yes, I'm sure.
Three-fifty.
3.141592653589.
793238462643383279
I know.
I eat that every morning with a smile on my face.
I didn't know about that skill for a minute.
Oh, it's cold.
Is it cold?
They're big. I knew it.
Most macaroons are this big.
Wow!
Wow, amazing!
They're so cute!
Ta-da!
Frozen animal macarons in salted milk flavor!
They say you can eat these frozen!
It's a new texture macaroon!
Looks delicious!
Pacarappa pacarappa pacarappa pacarappa!
Butter candy hot!
That's amazing!
Butter candy jumps!
I'm just a little concerned about the chocolate mint all of a sudden.
It tastes amazing!It tastes amazing.
Amazing I've never seen anything like this.
It's so pretty.
Strawberry milk, Pasquitos and eggs.
Looks delicious.
So cute.
Oh, here it is.
Pikachu's book.
Wow, that long one.
I can't do it.
I studied Picasso as a hobby in elementary school.
I forgot some of it, but I made it just in time.
That's great.
Oh, wow.
Wow, the box is kind of cute.
It's cute.
Wow!
Wow.
It's so cute.
Wow, it's in small portions.
It's a lot of small portions. There's three of them.
You can share it.
I'm kind of curious about Idima.
Well, I'm going to have some.
Bon appétit.
It smells so minty.
It's good.
Is it good?
Chocolate mint.
Yum, yum, yum.
I'll have some myself.
It's so good.
So much chocolate mint!So much chocolate mint!
This is delicious!
I'm curious about the other flavors, too!
I want to save it every time I come to Sendai!
I want to!
It's delicious!
Delicious!
Pakarang, pakarang, pakarang, pakarang, pakarang!
I don't really understand
End-Chain T-shirts
I heard that they sell endochene T-shirts at EV2.
I heard that the color of this one also changes depending on the season.
It's blue because it's summer now.
Cool!
I want to buy one, right?
Yeah, I want to buy one.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is there anything in there?
What? What? What?
Ehhhh...
It's in there!
Is that possible?
Ehhhhhh...
Pakarappa-karappa-karappa-karappa-karappa.
So, here we are.
I introduced the vending machine at E Beanz's first game.
I introduced the vending machine.
Wow, it was amazing!
There were so many kinds of vending machines.
If you come to Sendai for the first time, please visit E-Beanz!
Hey, Mr. E Beanz!Hey, Mr. E. Beanz.
There's a row of vending machines on the first floor.
I hope you will all check it out!
I think so.
Well, anyway...
I've come all the way to Sendai.
I'm going to enjoy Sendai after this!
I'm sure I will.
Okay, bye bye everyone!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe and rate my channel!
Shimmy!
Horse!
Oh!